[Music] I have
[Música]
n't called Delos
a delos no lo he llamado
because
porque
Ah That's true eh cones also it's been a
Ah Es verdad eh conos también hace una
while since I last spoke, I think I haven't
jta de tiempo que no hablo creo que no
spoken since he was in Japan or he was
hablo desde que estaba él en Japón o se
leaving for Japan. I think I think it was when
iba para Japón Creo que creo que fue
he was at the airport in Japan the
estando él en el aeropuerto pa Japón la
last time I spoke to him I'm
última vez que hablé con él estoy
losing my friends eh I'm
perdiendo mis amistades eh estoy
losing my friends completely
perdiendo mis amistades completamente
but it's that I haven't called him either or I haven't
pero es que no le llamado tampoco ni le
spoken to him to get him to come here
he hablado para que venga para acá
because there's nothing either it's just that
porque es que no hay nada tampoco está
the gossip is a little you know
es que el salseo está un poco sabes a
what it is what are the
ver qué es lo que
headlines about David Suarez what are the
qué titulares hay de David Suárez qué
headlines about David Suarez it hasn't been
titulares hay de David Suárez no ha sido
anything either you know let's see
tampoco una cosa que me sabes a ver
let's see
vamos a ver
[Music]
[Música]
this is an interesting topic and also there's
este hay un tema interesante y además
a lot of food coming up because you
viene viene bastante colación porque tú
're sitting here today by the way I
estás hoy sentado aquí por cierto Me
got a Twitter that I don't know if it was Javier
salió un Twitter que no sé si era Javier
Canino Javier Canino Javier Canino
canino Javier canino Javier canino
Javier HD one of the accounts of the
Javier HD una de las cuentas de de
bad guys of this jav
malitos de esta jav
canino ael canino this was
canino ael canino esto era
dude I can't guarantee it Does anyone know if
tío no lo garantizo Alguien sabe si ya
the Turbo lawsuit has arrived the truth is I
llegó la demanda Turbo la verdad es que
don't know neither I and  I'm carrying it, so
no lo sé ni yo y la llevo yo o sea que
Ah damn, let me see, it hasn't
Ah conchin déjame ver todavía no ha
arrived yet, what about it hasn't arrived yet, I think it's
llegado lo de todavía no ha llegado creo
not in response to this, uh, to the
que no es en respuesta a esto eh a lo de
turboplane thing, the response, let's see, who
turboplane que la respuesta a ver quién
knows if the turboplane lawsuit has arrived yet, not even
sabe si ya llegó la demanda turboplane
me and I'm carrying it here, the truth
ni yo y la llevo yo hasta aquí la verdad
is that I don't even know and I'm carrying it or
es que no lo sé ni yo y la llevo yo o
so Ah and and here I think he's
sea que Ah y y aquí creo que está
talking about something else, let's see, it hasn't
hablando de otra cosa a ver no ha
arrived, see, I know, I know more or less what
llegado a ver yo sé yo sé más o menos lo
happened, see, it
que pasó a ver puesta está pero es que
's posted but it's that people believe that the lawsuits are uh people believe that the lawsuits are I wish Look if you knew that last week, no, the other one, I think, one arrived that I believed because I was saying, wow, it takes them so long to respond to
diciendo [__] que tardan en responder
one that I put in November or December or
una que puse en noviembre o diciembre o
something like that and and and and the thing is that they had rejected
algo así y y y y es que habían rechazado
the address that we gave And they
la dirección que nosotros dimos Y la
sent it back and the court started
mandaron de vuelta y el juzgado se puso
to uh look for another one somewhere else to
a eh buscar otra a otro sitio donde
notify a move like that happened, you know and and
notificar una movida así pasó sabes y y
the week, I mean, justice is really slow,
la semana o sea es lentísimo la justicia
I, this issue of lawsuits, let's see
yo el tema este de las demandas m a ver
in the  Turbo plan case with Delos, of course, let's
en el caso de Turbo plan con delos claro
see, if Delos has asked him to
a ver es que si delos le ha pedido
rectify and the guy keeps calling him a
rectificar y el tío No para de llamarle
scammer, scammer, scammer, well, let's
estafador estafador estafador pues ya a
see, my son, if I'm telling you and
ver hijo mío si te lo estoy diciendo y
no longer and he continues, well, of course there's no
ya no y sigue pues ya Claro que no queda
other choice, but as long as they can, always,
otra pero mientras que se puedan siempre
Hey, fix it and not get to that because the thing is that,
Oye arreglar y no llegar a eso porque es
then it's that this is going to take
que es que luego es que esto va a tardar
4 years, man, 5 years, you go and know how long it's
4 años tío 5 años vete tú a sab lo que
going to take, three, two, whatever they want to
va a tardar tres dos lo que quieran
extend if there are resources and things, no,
alargar si hay recursos y cosas no
eh. Let's see in the case of Turboplane, well,
eh A ver en el caso de turboplane los
maybe the truth is, in
Pues a lo mejor sí la verdad dentro de
a year and a half, two, the Plex, but Thank you very much,
un año y medio dos el plexpero Muchas
thanks to dude, dude,
gracias gracias a tiparraco tiparraco
came to the podcast, you had a show, I
vino al podcast tú tenías un show yo
had a ticket to the show because I had been
tenía entrada en el show porque había
supporting Vincent Fish 10 years
estado apoyando Vincent Fish 10 años
later and I said, wow, I would be very
después y decía ostras me haría mucha
excited to meet Dez in person. I
ilusión poder conocer a dez en persona
said, dude, you who know him. No,
dije tiparraco tú que lo conoces No
now we'll see what, what does he know you from,
ahora veremos de qué de qué te conoce
among many things, I said, can you put me
entre muchas cosas dije Me puedes poner
in touch, he did it? Here you are, there I was
en contacto lo hizo Aquí estás ahí te
able to meet you. So dude, greetings and since
pude conocer Así que tipa un saludo y ya
we're talking about  guy What happened in the
que hablamos de tiparraco Qué pasó en el
dog fight eh with the famous one actually
dog Fight eh con el famoso efectivamente
okay eh nothing eh really let's see It's that
vale eh nada eh realmente a ver Es que
this
esto se ha hablado ya mucho y me sabe un
has been talked about a lot and I feel a little bad because the turkey in the end I think he really screwed himself when really the summary is he had a bad day that's how villains begin eh with a bad day guy he was about to become the Joker and no what he did
convertirse en el Joker y no lo que hizo
was eh Let's see guy he went too far that
fue eh A ver tiparraco se le fue esa
night he went too far he went too far that
noche se le fue tela se le fue tela eso
was very ridiculous what he did lisar and
fue muy ridículo lo que hizo lizarse y
now he's much better than I saw him in the
ahora está mucho mejor que lo vi en el
rewind and and and I don't know He's as he is as
rewind y y y no sé Está está como está
always but it's true that that day he
como siempre pero es verdad que ese día
had drunk I believe that thing about there being nothing but
pues había bebido yo me creo lo de que
alcohol I got that
no hubiese más que alcohol me me dio esa
feeling like this person is
sensación como de esta persona va
drunk she's not into anything else and yes I
borracha no va de otra cosa y sí me
remember arriving at the event and he and
acuerdo llegar al evento y estaban él y
Antonio García Villarán and a couple of
Antonio García villarán y un par de
other people were there and I remember that I
personas más y me recuerdo que me
approached him and since I know him the
acerqué y como tengo confianza con él lo
first thing I said to him was Hey do I have a
primero que le dije es Oye tengo algún
joke for you I said something like that and he
chiste para ti Algo así le dije y me
said you are mar that was before
dijo tú eres mar eso fue antes
deo the guy like Yeah the guy the guy was
deo el tío como Sí el tío el tío estaba
like this it was like his running ha or est
como este era como su running ha o est
was his thing I don't know it was like the one from the day It
era su cosa no sé era como el del día
was that yes but that we get along that he
Era ese sí pero que nos llevamos bien
said that but I understand that it was the same
que dijo eso pero entiendo que era igual
as when I make jokes about him at the
que cuando yo hago chistes de él en el
roost or whatever and nothing and at no
roost o lo que sea y nada y en ningún
point did I think it was then like to
momento yo pensé que fuese luego como a
say I think it's a good moment I know I think
a decir creo que es un buen momento se
the summary is what
yo creo el resumen es lo que lo explicó
he explained I think in the podcast the good summary of
él Creo en el podcast el buen resumen de
everything is he said You'll see what How
todo es él dijo Ya verá queé Qué
funny is this going to be I mean I think it
gracioso va a ser esto O sea yo creo que
's the pantom meme f in his head it was
es el meme de pantom f en su cabeza era
spectacular I think this is the summary
espectacular Creo que este es el resumen
of of of everything I mean I think the guy at
de de de todo o sea creo que el tío en
a given moment he says This is going to be the
un momento dado é dice Esto va a ser la
host and spoiler it wasn't but it's over
[__] y spoiler no lo fue pero ya está
later eh I apologize Shortly after
luego eh Me pido disculpas Poco después
and
y
your relationship is good to this day everything at
vua relación bien a día de hoy todo en
some point your relationship was seen
algún momento se vio vuestra relación
Perhaps harmed by that
Quizás perjudicada por ese
event No man I was
acontecimiento No hombre yo estaba
waiting for the next day for him to tell me
esperando al día siguiente que me dijese
something because of course The guy apologized to
algo porque claro El tío se disculpó con
Jordi He apologized to everyone and I
Jordi Se disculpó con todo el mundo y yo
eh  you have screwed me either, you screwed me anything. In fact, I
eh has jod tampoco me jod nada Es más yo
think the one thing is that with Jordi he
creo que lo una cosa es que con Jordi
lowered his head, dude, rac, that I didn't
agachó la cabeza tipar rac que yo no lo
understand, he says he didn't apologize to Jordi,
entendí dice no se disculpó con Jordi
with everyone yes, Jordi said that
con todo el mundo sí Jordi dijo que que
what he would have hit him no or that he
que lo que le hubiera pegado no o que le
or that he wanted to slap him or something
o que le quería pegar un guantazo o algo
like that he said No, it was cool, what's that
así dijo No estuvo Guay que es que
when I finish the roast, the first of the
yo cuando acabe el roast el primero del
first do Fight, when I get off, my friends tell me,
primer do Fight al bajarme me dicen mis
man, you're a tring topic and I do,
colegas tío eres tring topic y yo sí
but the first topic in Spain, no, the
pero primer topic de España no el
first, you're a guy, which is good
primero es tiparraco lo cual está bien
because Javi and the guys from SS connection who
porque Javi y a los de SS connection que
call him a scammer to his face and say
lo llaman estafador en su cara y dicen
that they don't rectify because he doesn't report them,
que no rectifican porque no los denuncia
delox, well, I imagine they'll end up
delox pues yo me imagino que acabarán
too, I mean, after the debate, I don't know
también o sea después del debate no sé
what happened with Pablo on that. The
en qué quedó deos con Pablo en eso La
truth is, I have no [ __ ] idea, but it's what I
verdad no tengo ni [__] idea pero es lo
told you. I mean, in the end, the issue
que os he dicho O sea al final el tema
of the lawsuits has to be an issue
de las demandas tiene que ser ya un tema
that has you really fed up with it and the
que te tenga muy hasta la [__] y que la
person is that you no longer know what I'm
persona es que ya no sabes lo que te
talking about. I mean, no, I  I would actually look into the SS connection thing,
digo O sea no yo lo de SS connection sí
but eh. Also in
lo vería la verdad Pero eh También en
part the profile of SS connection, let's see
parte el perfil de SS connection a ver
how I can tell you. They are characters that I don't know
cómo os lo digo Son personajes que no sé
if they are to be taken seriously, like suing
si son para tomar en serio como demandar
Mario Tiberian, not for what he tells you,
al Mario tiberian no por lo que te diga
taking what Mario Tiberian says seriously, you
tomarte en serio lo que diga el Mario
know, but eh. It depends on how he
tiberian sabes pero ya eh Depende como
wakes up one day, how it crosses you, you know,
te levant un día como se te cruce sabes
but it's already an issue that has you fed
pero ya es un tema que te tenga hasta la
up or that you're already trying, there are
[__] o que ya estés intentando hay
people who don't stop, eh, I mean, there are people who don't
gente que no para eh o sea hay gente que
stop, there are people that you say, [ __ ], man, come on, I'm not looking at him, come on, come on, it's over tomorrow, he won't
no para hay gente que tú dices [__]
answer anymore tomorrow he won't tell me anymore and it goes
está mañana ya no contestará más mañana
on and on and on and on and
ya no me dice más y sigue y sigue y
there, since these are things that have to be that,
sigue y sigue y ahí ya que son cosas que
but it's what I'm
tienen que ser eso pero es lo que te
telling you, it has to be a brake because
digo tiene que ser una frenada porque
now imagine the two of them, those two turkeys,
ahora imagínate los dos los dos pavos
no. Now imagine that they sue him
esos no Ahora imagínate que lo demandan
now that they notify them because then you have to
ahora que los notifiquen porque luego
locate him, that they
tienes que tienes que localizarlo que
notify that I don't know what, eh, man,
que notifiquen que no sé qué eh tío la
Loli Huerta is this one that is a
Loli Huerta es esta que esa es una
lawsuit that you say, a lady who  she
demanda que dices t una una señora que
stuck months and months yelling at the
se pegó meses y meses gritándole a la
camera calling me an abuser stalker
cámara diciéndome maltratador acosador
[ __ ] garbage pig eh of but but in an
[__] basura cerdo eh of pero pero en
insult way well the other day I saw her
plan insulto bueno el otro día la vi
yelling at the camera telling a
gritando a la cámara diciéndole a una
woman if your mother has died if your
mujer si tu madre se ha muerto si la
[ __ ] filthy mother has died let
[__] [__] de tu madre se ha muerto que
the worms eat her well and now the
se la coman los gusanos pues y ahora la
lady got all super haughty not
señora se puso en plan super altiva no
saying come on come sue me but
diciendo venga venga demándame pero
sue me sue me I'll give you the
demándame demándame yo te doy la
address and precisely we have a
dirección y precisamente tenemos un
problem with that that we have
problema con eso que la que la le hemos
given her Two two different addresses and she does
puesto Ya dos dos direcciones diferentes
n't answer the lawsuit okay two
y no la coge la demanda vale dos
different addresses and she doesn't answer the
direcciones diferente y no la coge la
lawsuit I don't know if it's because she doesn't open it to the
demanda no sé si es que no le Abre al
mailman if they are and I know or a relative opens it and
cartero si son y sé o abre un familiar y
says that she doesn't live there I don't know okay
dice que ella no vive yo que sé vale
but we are having to see the problem
pero estamos teniendo a ver el problema
with that there will come a time when I
con eso ya llegará un momento en el que
think Pablo told me that since there will come a
creo que me dijo Pablo que ya que llega
time since if not I know that if because
un momento ya que si no s que si porque
Also she acts super cocky in the
Además ella se pone como super chula en
live shows it doesn't reach me it doesn't reach me send it to me send it to me he
los directos a mí no me llega a mí no me
spoke to her  Pablo
llega mándamela mándamela le habló Pablo
on WhatsApp and said Look, you
por por WhatsApp y le dijo Mira que
're asking live for us to
estás pidiendo en directo que te
send you the lawsuit, take it and it's in
mandemos la demanda toma y que está en
this court at this number ta ta ta ta
este juzgado en este número ta ta ta ta
in case you want to take it and here you have
por si la quieres [__] y toma aquí
a copy, on WhatsApp everyone has it,
tienes una copia por Whats todo la tiene
well I don't open it, well I don't and he doesn't
pues no la abro pues no la y no la
want to take it. So I understand, because I
quiere [__] Entonces yo entiendo ya que
understand that if there comes a time when
entiendo que si llega un momento en el
you are giving it, you know that they
que tú estás dando que la sabes que te
are notifying you on WhatsApp, by email
están notificando por WhatsApp por email
everywhere that you are saying
por todas partes que tú estás diciendo
that they should send it to you, that you know you have it
que te la manden que sabes que la tienes
there in that game at that number that you don't
ahí en ese jugado en ese número que no
want to take it and that no postman wants to open it,
la quieres [__] y que no quieres abrir
well I understand that
ningún cartero pues entiendo que se hace
the trial is held, you know, eh, Without your defense, it's
el juicio sabes eh Sin tu defensa es que
something else you don't know, but it's a lot of laziness, it
otra cosa no sabes pero es mucha pereza
's a lot of prey. I generally prefer
es mucha presa yo prefiero por lo
and that's what I'm going to try until,
general y es lo que voy a intentar hasta
well not with everything, eh, I mean, I've filed, it
que bueno no con todo eh o sea he puesto
's no secret that I've filed this
no es ningún secreto que he puesto este
in the last six months a few
en los últimos seis meses unas cuantas
lawsuits that have already gone and still don't
de demandas que ya Iran y todavía no
have a hearing for any of them. I
tienen ni audiencia pra ninguna de ellas
sued Loli, this in December, I
demandé a la Loli esta en diciembre
sued another YouTuber who got into a mess making
demandé a otro youtuber que se lió hacer
some  direct saying a series of mind-
unos directos diciendo una serie de
blowing barbarities to another since he had been doing it for
barbaridades flipante a otro ya que
years, I already sent another one who didn't
llevaba años dem mandé ya a otro que no
stop, who had been doing it for years and that's it and that's it three three lawsuits
paraba que llevaba años y ya está y ya
three lawsuits I have
está tres tres demandas tres demandas
right now and I don't know right
tengo puesto yo ahora mismo y no sé
now I was undermining another
ahora mismo estaba minando a otra
person I was undermining but the truth is that
persona estaba miná pero la verdad es
nothing more than having to waste
que nada más que el tenerme que perder
time on that man with all the work I
el tiempo en eso tío con la de trabajo
have man nothing more than wasting time
que tengo tío nada más que el perder el
on that giving myself those
tiempo en eso entregarme esos
live shows is that pathetic content
directos es es ese contenido patético
for minutes as later I get p for
para minuta como después me pongo p para
me it is important this you know it's what
mí tiene importancia esto sabes es lo
I value because it's time Maybe I
que yo valoro porque es tiempo A lo
invest in working You know they are
mejor que invierto en trabajar Sabes son
all the barbarities that I said, I mean it
todas las barbaridades que yo dije o sea
saved my ass a little in the sense
me salvó un poco el culo en el sentido
that I didn't get much hate or
de que de que no me cayó mucho odio ni
anything And it was thanks to him how lazy
ni tal Y fue gracias a que él qué pereza
Yeah yeah Karim There is one that I have halfway through a
Sí sí Karim Hay una que la tengo a media
minute and I don't know if I will continue the truth
de minutar y no sé si seguiré la verdad
because it seems that he has
porque se parece ser que se ha dado
realized a little bit of the mistake he has made
cuenta un poco de la pata que ha metido
and I think he has removed the videos too
y creo que ha quitado los vídeos también
so I don't know if I will continue the truth I
entonces no sé si continuaré la verdad
went  minute while I was
fui minut mientras que estaba
taking advantage of the hour flight hours and
aprovechando las hor horas de vuelo y
things like that you know but I don't know if I'll continue The
cosas así sabes pero no sé si seguiré La
truth is I'm very busy man really I
verdad estoy muy ocupado tío de verdad O
mean if the last thing I want eh if the
sea si yo lo que menos quiero eh si yo
last thing I want is those kinds of
lo que menos quiero son ese tipo de
problems and to me whoever doesn't fix
problemas y a mí me quien no arregla las
things with me is because they love us
cosas conmigo es porque nos quiere vale
okay if you go looking for me you go looking for me you go
cl si me vas buscando me vas buscando me
looking for me well in the end when they
vas buscando pues al final cuando me
find me the problem with a lot of
encuentre es que el problema con mucha
people is that they get obsessed and they freak out
gente es eso se obsesionan y se rayan
when you expose them okay or when you
cuando cuando les expones vale o cuando
answer them you leave them in a bad way and they are
les respondes los dejas mal y se quedan
affected for life you ignore it you don't
tocado de por vida pasas de ello no
answer And then it's like they
contestas Y entonces es como que se
get carried away they get carried away they get carried away
vienen arriba se vienen arriba se vienen
and they leave you and now then when
arriba y te van y ahora luego cuando
the day comes that you wake up one day in a
llegue el día que tú te levantes un día
worse mood or whatever or you say
de peor humor o lo que sea o ya digas tú
Look well I'm going to put you in your place
Mira pues ya te voy a poner en tu sitio
you say four things and you look bad and you
le digas cuatro cosas y queden mal y
look super exposed now
quedes super expuesto ahora venderá otra
the crying will sell again and another time that there is that they have
vez los llantos y otra vez que hay que
put you there is another time that you are
te han puesto hay otra vez que teis
exposed man well [ __ ] if nobody
expuesto hombre pues [__] si nadie te
is telling you anything you know if nobody
está diciendo nada sabes si nadie te
is telling you anything he stops he exploded it was a
está diciendo nada se para petó fue un
little  shield So I'm
poco el escudo O sea que yo yo para
taking advantage of this to give you a little promo since I like you
hacerte un poco de promo aprovecho ya
eh if
que me caes bien eh si realmente la
people really think that the Rose you play in
gente le parece que el Rose que haces en
Dog Fight is strong they should go see your
dog Fight es fuerte que vayan a ver tu
show I don't think I've ever laughed that much I
show yo creo que no me he reído tanto a
must also say that dark humor
mí también cabe decir que el humor negro
is one of my weaknesses I've never laughed so much
es una de mis debilidades no me he reído
in a show as with yours
nunca tanto en un show como con el tuyo
eh My dates on my social networks
eh Mis fechas en mis redes sociales
go there Of course take advantage take advantage I
métanse por ahí Claro que apr aprovecha
also wanted to tell you
aprovecha te quería decir también
regarding this that of course I saw it
respecto a esto que claro yo lo vi
when it was airing on YouTube and I
cuando se estaba emitiendo en YouTube y
said wow what a mess is going on but I
dije ostras la que se está liando pero
thought it's going to be noted you at the
pensé va a quedar en anota tú en el
moment when you're doing the
momento en el que estás haciendo el
roast And you see that happens what's the
roast Y ves que sucede eso qué es lo
first thing that goes through your head eh I
primero que pasa por tu cabeza eh yo
think it's a joke and it was a joke
pienso que es una coña y era una coña
but I think it was a joke like
pero yo pienso que era una coña que como
when you scream you're at a wedding and there's
cuando gritas estás en una boda y
always a slightly drunk friend
siempre hay un colega un poco borracho
who says a cheer to the bride and groom he says
que dice un viva a los novios lo dice
some [ __ ] like that but you say it
alguna gilipollez así como pero lo dices
once you don't say it many times
una vez no lo dices muchas veces
so I think that's what  he failed him it's
entonces creo que ahí lo que le falló es
then or rather I think that neither or rather
luego o sea creo que tampoco o sea
maybe it wasn't an incredible joke But
quizás no era una broma increíble Pero
perhaps the problem was not to rebuke
quizás tampoco el problema era increpar
the comedian because there are times that that happens
al cómico porque hay veces que eso pasa
in live shows because someone
en los shows en vivo pues alguien te
can shout something at you, they can say something to you The
puede gritar algo te puede decir el
problem is when someone is very heavy it
problema es cuando alguien es muy pesado
is and I think that to him like when I
es y yo creo que a él como cuando
understand When you are drunk there is this
entiendo Cuando vas borracho hay este
point like from Him Time passes
punto como de El El tiempo pasa de otra
differently I think that he thought he was
forma Yo creo que él pensó que estaba
being less heavy than he could be that's it
siendo menos pesado de lo que podía ser
but I I at no moment
ya está pero yo Yo en ningún momento
thought he is trying to screw me over this that it
pensé me está queriendo [__] esto que
wasn't like that either eh I thought he was making
tampoco era así eh pensé está haciendo
a joke and now he is repeating it
una broma y ahora la está repitiendo
again many times for some reason and that's
otra vez muchas veces por algún motivo y
a bit of it in the end I think that
ya está un poco eso al final yo creo que
obviously well he said it himself when he
obviamente bueno el mismo lo dijo cuando
came here he in his head it was
vino aquí él en su cabeza era
spectacular then it was not like that
espectacular luego pues no fue así no
nothing happens a drunken mistake can be
pasa nada un error de borracho lo puede
anyone The bad luck is not
tener cualquiera La mala pata no es
doing it in front of so many people that
hacerlo delante de tantísima gente esa
is the small difference I think that you
es la pequeña diferencia Yo creo que tú
go with any friend surely the
vas con cualquier colega seguramente la
night that you fell on top of yourself some friend of
noche que te cabaste encima algún colega
yours said some outrageous thing too
tuyo dijo cualquier barbaridad también
In the end I do not think that it is necessary to
Al final tampoco creo que haya que
exaggerate so much however once you
exagerar tanto sin embargo una vez tú
later see the networks you see that  it's trending
luego ves las redes ves que es trending
topic you expected that
topic tú te esperabas la que se iba a
all this was going to get complicated it's that with me it's not a
liar de todo esto es que conmigo no se
mess at all and it's a big mess with him
Lio para nada y se Lio un huevo con él
yes it is I mean I understand that sea is
sí que se O sea yo entiendo que mar es
a sensitive word I also didn't see an
una palabra sensible tampoco vi un rollo
excessively humiliating thing towards uh the
excesivamente vejatorio hacia eh la
lgtbi community I didn't see a thing about him
comunidad lgtbi no vi un rollo de él
telling all the people that he was
diciendo todas las personas que estaba
drunk and messed up and painted it that's it I mean
borracho y metió la pata y la pintó ya
no there weren't more
está O sea no tampoco había más
homosexuals they seem to me it wasn't like it
homosexuales me parecen no era como una
was yelling something that seems to me In 2024
era gritar algo que me parece En 2024
so little insult is so it's so poor the
tan poco insulto es tan es tan pobre la
word already and they have appropriated it in a
palabra ya y se le han apropiado de una
quite intelligent way uh
forma bastante inteligente eh
precisely they like now it seems like
precisamente ellos como que ahora parece
a meme it's almost like almost like a
un meme es casi como un casi como una
scrub I mean it seems to me like I think it would
fregar O sea me parece como a mí creo
n't seem too much like brother-
que no me parecería demasiado cu no de
in-law even you can do it it's like if I
cuñado incluso tú lo puedes es como si O
mean no no no it doesn't seem like an
sea no no me no me parece una cosa
alarming thing or anything it seemed more like a
alarmante ni ni nada me pareció más un
how annoying you are Shut your
rollo de qué cansino eres Cállate la
mouth roll more than a roll of this no eh you
boca más que un rollo de esto no eh
know it seemed to me more like Shut up it
sabes me pareció más como de Cállate me
seemed more like a bore than a bad type of
pareció más de pesado que de de mal tipo
But  He himself has realized and
de Pero él mismo se ha dado cuenta y
when it is that when you are drunk
cuando es que cuando estás borracho a
sometimes you become heavy it is a roll it is
veces te vuelves pesado es es de rollo
usually like that what are we going to say
suele ser así qué le vamos a decir
surely any of us a
seguramente cualquiera de nosotros un
bad drunken day well it has been a
día de borrachera malo pues ha sido un
heavy too clo Who has shouted sea
pesado también clo Quién ha gritado mar
drunk I surely not chicka more times
borrach yo no seguramente tipa más veces
but the point is I believe in empathizing
pero el punto está yo creo en empatizar
I think that later we will talk a little about
yo creo que luego hablaremos un poco de
how the networks are losing that
cómo las redes están perdiendo Quiz esa
empathy you In fact because of a joke it has
empatía tú De hecho por un chiste ha
been a trial you know it is crazy then
sido un juicio sabes es una locura luego
I want to go deeper into it Oh
quiero profundizar de lleno en ello Ah
[ __ ] it is true the subject of the trial
ostia es verdad el tema de lo del juicio
is true
es verdad
[Music]
[Música]